This is awful.
I wonder if Auntie Stella and the guys
at the construction site are okay.
Looks like the guild
made it through somehow.
It's been a while since I've taken
a good look at this signboard.
An adventurer, huh?
You didn't get one decent skill?!
You spent a full three-month term
practicing at every training school,
and you couldn't get a single one?
Noor, sorry...
but I can't let you register
as an adventurer like that.
I never imagined I'd reunite
with my instructors from back then.
I last saw them, what,
fifteen years ago?
Clays Royal Capital - 15 Years Ago
Let me train as a swordsman!
Train?
You?
Do you have a permit from
the Adventurer's Guild?
I just got one from the guildmaster!
The training is intense.
Are you prepared to bear with it?
Yes!
That's enough!
Tomorrow's going to be even more intense.
He'll be lucky to last three days.
It's day 10 now, huh?
At the very least, the tenacity of this kid
is definitely nothing to scoff at.
Next!
Never drop your sword,
even if you break a bone!
The enemy will not wait for you!
Hard to believe his eyes
are still so full of vigor
after getting his body and
mind put through the wringer!
This kid might actually have
a promising future.
Instructor!
When will I get to learn a skill?
That isn't something I decide.
Can you at least show me
what kind of skill I might get?
How was that?
A-amazing!
I couldn't see most of it!
Yeah, that figures.
It's a swift-foot technique that makes
my slashes difficult for even me to follow.
A boy like this probably
couldn't even see me with his bare eyes-
You kept the same rhythm the entire time.
Like whoosh, slash, sa-sa-slash!
Steady like a clock!
Whoosh, slash, sa-sa-slash!
Such latent potential.
If nurtured properly, he could match me...
Whoosh, slash, sa-sa-slash!
no, surpass me, even!
2 Months After
Training Started
How strange.
Parry!
Why hasn't he been able
to learn a skill aside from Parry?
All he needs is one.
Just one skill that
could be considered useful...
3 Months After
Training Started
That's enough, Noor.
Unfortunately-
Wait! Just give me a little longer-
There's no point.
Going any further would
be a waste of your time.
Parry isn't enough for someone
to make it as a swordsman.
Alas.
It seems Swordsmanship is the one thing
he didn't have the aptitude for.
Perhaps it would be better
if you chose another path.
Your talent may be found
in another training school.
I'm sure there's another path
for this child.
Whoa, whoa.
Are you serious about taking part
in my training regiment, kid?
The swordsman instructor
told me to try somewhere else.
Sig did, huh?
I had heard he was looking
after some kid, but...
He looks small enough
to get blown away by a light breeze.
I want to be an adventurer,
no matter what!
The role of a warrior is
to become the shield for their allies.
You understand that?
Yeah!
All right, let's give it a go.
2 Months After
Training Started
I'll give the boy credit,
I never thought he'd get this far.
Damn, talk about being tough AND gutsy!
If he just acquired a skill,
I could raise this kid
to be a literal invincible shield...
3 Months After
Training Started
Sorry, Noor.
I can keep going!
I acknowledge your efforts,
but what you have acquired is a slight
improvement of your physical abilities.
If you force yourself to continue on,
you will lose your life.
I know it sucks, but you gotta move on.
He's toughed it out more than most.
He deserves to be where
his efforts will get rewarded.
Please let me train here.
You really wanna do this?
Yes!
Well, if you insist.
Okay, here.
Try to throw it over there.
That sure is far.
Just do it.
After he misses, I'll just make up
a random reason to reject him.
I can already tell he'll be the
troublesome type of studen-
Was that okay?
Do it again.
Perfect.
Yeah, right!
This is the exact opposite of perfect!
Instructor, why am I doing nothing
but throwing stones?
Because I just know
you're gonna be trouble, duh!
I wanna use a bow.
Okay, get a good grip on it
and then assume the shooting position.
A good grip? Like thi-
Why'd it break?!
That's what I was afraid of...
Give me a break already, kid!
We're all out of training bows now,
so just use mine.
This one shouldn't break
no matter how strong he-
Just stick to throwing stones, got it?!
Okay.
2 Months After
Training Started
Where did you learn to do that?
Nobody taught me.
This is just how I've always hunted birds.
The super colorful ones
that like to swoop down from the sky
to grab mountain rabbits.
You've got to be kidding me...
That's a thunderflash!
It's difficult for even a seasoned hunter
with a superior bow
to bring those things down...
Although, I could totally do it
with my eyes closed.
Is there any point in him being here?
Your term is over.
3 Months After
Training Started
Get out of here.
Huh?! But I haven't learned anything ye-
You totally lack the sense
to handle any sort of delicate weaponry!
Just settle for throwing stones.
Such a pain in the butt.
You've already got enough to hack it
even without a bow.
I see.
You're the Noor I've heard about.
Sure, why not.
Huh? Are you sure?
Come with me.
We're starting right away.
Sense the enemy's presence.
And sneak up on them
without making a single sound.
He isn't bad.
All right!
Ow!
You'll have to do better than that!
There are various traps
rigged along this corridor.
Avoid falling into any of those traps
and make your way to this
hard-to-open treasure chest!
Avoid the traps, huh?
Got it!
Parry!
Stone Throw!
Incredible.
But, uh...
he's missing the point of the exercise.
You failed to dismantle the traps
leading to the treasure chest
3 Months After
Training Started
and your situational awareness
is poorly lacking.
There is no hope of you becoming a spy.
But even so, this boy has stamina
and tenacity that is beyond comparison.
Those are good qualities to have.
If he ever gives up on becoming an
adventurer,
I'll extend him an invite to join
the royal capital's intelligence agency.
Oh ho?
You're quite a young applicant,
aren't you?
I'm sure there was an age requirement
of at least 15 years old...
I got a permit from the Guildmaster,
and I've already trained
at the other schools.
It didn't work out, though.
Oh ho!
2 Months After
Training Started
Well, it seems the reason
you struggle to use magic
is because there's no mana
flowing through you in the first place.
Why doesn't it flow through me?
Perhaps you were just born that way.
In which case,
the only hope of changing that is for you
to go inside the Mana Resonance Room.
Mana Reso-what?
Let me give it a shot!
Well, I suppose you can.
But leave immediately
if it starts feeling too intense.
He hasn't come out yet?!
No, sir.
Th-that isn't good!
That room drastically amplifies
all of the human senses
and he's been in there for days?!
It could kill him if we're not careful!
Noor!
What is it?
A-are you okay?
Anything wrong with your body?
Not at all.
Don't interrupt me.
I feel like I'm close
to having a breakthrough.
Huh?
This is the only spell I learned...
3 Months After
Training Started
Oh ho.
It's astonishing that Tiny Flame
is all you've gotten after months of training.
It's rare to see people
as incapable of magic as you are.
But, given your lack of mana,
it's actually impressive
how far you've come.
What?!
Am I seeing this right?!
I-is he dual casting?!
It took me 50 years to get to that point,
yet he managed it on his own
in just three months?!
This won't help me be an adventurer.
Indeed it won't.
Turns out this isn't
the place for you, huh?
It's such a pity.
He has so much talent.
If only his body
was more attuned to magic,
he could have been known through
the land as an unparalleled magician.
First, let me ask you:
Did you undergo the rite of blessing
when you were a still a small child?
The rite? What's that?
Only students who were selected
in advance and undergo that rite
can train at this school.
I'm sorry.
I'm not leaving until you agree
to let me train here.
Do as you wish.
I'm not leaving until you agree
to let me train here.
Is that so?
He can't seriously intend
to stay there forever...
I will allow you to participate
in the basics of our training.
But you must understand
there is no guarantee
that you will actually learn a skill.
3 Months After
Training Started
That is most certainly Low Heal.
How is this even possible?
But...
Yes, unfortunately for you,
Low Heal won't be recognized as a
serviceable skill to become an adventurer.
That figures.
I didn't have any luck here, either...
Although it only works on scratches,
it's impressive you can use low-level
healing magic without a natural blessing.
He performed a miracle on his own
without undergoing the rite or using
a holy spirit for an intermediary...
So, in a manner of speaking,
that means he can wield the
power of miracles without limit.
Master Sain! About Noor...
He's disappeared from the capital?!
I should have stopped him yesterday...
Well, we can just leave him be, right?
That kid's strong enough
to hack it on his own.
No.
If we invest our time
in nurturing his gifts,
then that boy will undoubtedly
become someone extraordinary.
Oh ho...
You're right about that.
I never imagined he was going through
the same thing at all the other schools...
We should all train him
and give him guidance.
That boy is overflowing with promise.
I have no objection to that.
Although that makes it
more difficult for me
to recruit him to
the intelligence agency...
I'm of the same opinion as Sain.
I am, too.
I guess if you guys insist...
How about you, Sig?
I'm heading off on a journey
to find Noor now.
Hey! Whoa, now!
I understand your eagerness,
but please calm down.
Now then, just to be clear:
As the Sovereign Six, we will take Noor in
and raise him as a group.
You all agree, right?
Then, let's get started
and look for him right away.
Oh, it's Noor!
Hello, sir, I'm glad you're safe.
Yeah, made it through somehow.
This was lying on the ground outside.
Oh, I guess it flew off.
Thanks.
Weren't you supposed to head to Mithra?
Oh, but I guess you saw what was
happening in the royal capital.
Yeah, I turned around and rushed back.
You're all caked in mud.
And your clothes are burned...
It was a hectic day.
I had to move around a lot.
Well, that's a disaster for ya.
Everybody's in the same boat.
I had an awful time, too.
I'm completely worn out too.
About that, Noor.
Hate to do this when you're so dog tired,
but the construction guild boss
has been searching high and low for you.
He needs ya to haul away some rubble and
help build temporary housing and the like.
I figured that would be the case.
That's why I came.
Where is he?
I'll get you a map. Take it with you.
Having you here is a huge help!
When you're here
our progress is off the charts!
Glad I can help.
This really was a crazy day...
I went on a trip by carriage...
met Rolo...
I got sent flying by Lynne's magic...
and then I got sent flying
by Lynne's magic...
A bunch of stuff happened,
but getting sent flying by Lynne's magic
is what I remember the most...
I'm going to need some rest
and food pretty soon.
But I can't afford to quit just yet!
I'm sure you've already noticed,
but the Holy Theocracy of Mithra
was working behind the scenes
with Deridas on this war.
Yes.
From the minotaur incident to the
Magical Empire's weaponry,
high purity mana-stones that can
only be produced in that country
have been a factor at every possible turn.
Looking forward,
it seems our days won't be peaceful.
However, there are people
our nation can depend on.
And most importantly,
right now, we have that man.
Thanks! Eat up!
Instructor Noor.
Thank you so much for yesterday.
I should be thanking you.
It was hard for you too, right?
Are you handing out provisions?
Yes.
I'm also treating those who are injured.
Are you here to help
with the restoration work?
Yeah.
I'm handing these out to everyone,
so have one if you like.
Can I really?
By all means!
Thanks.
I'm going back to distributing these,
so goodbye for now.
Okay. Good luck!
Thanks!
Don't overwork yourself, Instructor!
Man, I really wouldn't be where I am
without everybody's help.
Okay.
I can move much better now.
This is a really good, sturdy sword.
Although it won't see much flashy action,
as long as I'm holding onto it.
But in spite of everything,
I want to be an adventurer.
I want to go on adventures like the heroes
in the storybooks Dad read to me.
For right now, let me put you
to good use here.
Noor!
We've cleared out enough in this area!
Are you good to keep working elsewhere?
Sure thing!
#12 I Parry Everything
Parry!
Well, I guess this is where
my real work starts!